Welcome to another video and in this video, we are going to achieve our goal, our goal is
to execute the ransomware binary inside the target machine. So, in this video, we are going to do that, okay.
So, we did all the measures before the ransomware deployment like deleting the shadow copies
and modifying the boot options, etc. So, before deploying, before executing the ransomware binary,
you need to make sure, if you are trying in your VM, you need to make sure your network connection
and everything was disabled, okay. So, basically, you need to check if your
primary machine and your VM machine do not have any contact, okay. So, we know ransomware
binary, ransomware will easily spread across the state very easily through the SMBR, through the network.
You need to make sure everything, okay. So, I have disabled my network connections. So,
my VM machines do not have any contact with my primary machine, okay. So, also, I have disabled the
chat folder settings. There is no chat folder now. So, I have downloaded the ransomware binary from
the zoo repository from here. So, this, I would not suggest you to execute the ransomware
binary in your machine, but it will be very, very harmful thing if you are executing the ransomware
binary because we saw many, many tactics, your data will be accelerated and everything will be
happened and the database will be encrypted, okay. So, many of them know once the ransomware
binary was executed or the database will be encrypted, right. So, let us execute the ransomware
binary now. So, everything was ready and knowing that attacks us, okay. Let us execute this and
we will see what happens in the machine.
So, if you see the changes, so once I executed the ransomware binary, I got this file, right.
So, here, you can see here, banner cry, decryptor and let us open this document and you can see
the image which is saved. So, I was not able to open anything, okay, basically. So, my system was
completely freezed and I can't able to do anything, okay. So, my machine was completely frozen
and I can't able to do anything. So, let us check the download folders and we will see
that I will try to open the, this is a JPEG file, see the icon, how it looks like.
So, my photos, anything was not opening. So, it was, please read me. So, let us open the
please read me file and let us see what, what is inside the please read me. So, you can, you can see
the readme files here, what is wrong with my files, you put on files or encrypted it means you will
not able to access any more until they are decrypted, okay. So, please send $300 worth of Bitcoin
to this address, okay. So, we need to send $300 worth of Bitcoin to the address to decrypt, okay.
So, please find the application file name, banner, decrypt, decrypt, decryptor, software,
cancel, following information, etc, etc, okay. So, once you install the ransomware files in a binary,
we will automatically get a readme file and that readme files contain some information like,
so that readme files contain some information like how to decrypt and where we need to contact
to the, the threat actor, because the threat actor will give the, because the threat actor
will give the key to decrypt your software, okay. So, if let open with new document, you can see
the encryption here, new text to dogma.txt, WNCR, okay. So, WNCR, Y is a ransomware,
binary, sorry, ransomware extension, okay. So, you can see the image,
so here you can see the, give me a second,
so everything will be in WNCR and all,
so everything was basically encrypted, right. So, here you can find it's WNCR,
basically it will, it will encrypt all the things like pictures, documents, I do not have
any of the end of document as well as the picture to encrypt. So, you need to understand what
happens when see ransomware get, get into the machine, okay. So, every ransomware has been executed,
it will absolutely find the readme files like this or a key dot txt, please read me how to decrypt
or txt like that file. So, that file will contain information like how to decrypt and where,
how to contact the threat actor, okay. So, in our scenario, you never snare you,
we have successfully executed the ransomware binary into our target machine.
And so, that's all about this video, I need you to understand what's happened after
once the ransomware has been executed, okay. So, in our scenario, it was showing the Windows team,
but in, it's a safe file, I just took it from the, these tests to file for our ransomware,
want to cry. If you face the real attack, this icon has been changed to some others, okay.
So, that you can definitely, you can research in Google. So, what happens after the ransomware?
So, I can't able to execute that in my environment, okay. So, that's all about this video
and hope you, how we understand this video. So, we are in a final stage,
almost we completed our red team operations. We will meet you in our next video. Thank you for
watching.